Max Bohm
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Motion Picture Film, Series 9:; (Box 6; 1 folder)
  A 16mm (positive) copy of a silent black and white motion picture film Six Foot Art, in Which Max Bohm, Member of the National Academy Tells How He Does It showing Max Bohm describing his method of preparing mentally and physically to create a painting. There is also a 35mm (negative) copy of this film.
  - Motion Picture Film Six Foot Art, in Which Max Bohm, Member of the National Academy Tells How He Does It, circa 1923 (Box 6 (hol), Folder 20)